beingamom.life 2016-10-12

# Privacy Policy | Being a Mom | Like it. Love it. Live it.

### Privacy Policy Statement

**Effective Date of Policy is November 6, 2012**

Fans Of Being a Mom, Inc. (“BAM”) knows that you are concerned about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. We are committed to giving you transparency of our privacy practices and control over your data. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

By visiting or using the BAM website ([http://beingamom.life](http://beingamom.life/)) (the BAM or the Site), BAM’s services and applications, and any other linked pages, features, or content offered from time to time by BAM in connection therewith (collectively, the “Site”), you, the user (“you” or “User”) acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

BAM is a Site providing and sharing both original and user-generated content about a variety of experiences related to motherhood.

Please take the time to familiarize yourself with the Privacy Policy as well as the Terms of Use

### **What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers BAM’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and other data (non-personally identifiable information) that BAM gathers when you are accessing BAM’s  Site.

### **What Doesn’t This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that BAM does not own or control, or to individuals that BAM does not employ or manage. In addition, should the Site contain links to outside sources, both those added by BAM and those submitted by Users, and while we attempt to provide links only to those sites that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any websites you visit and the third party applications you use. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Site.

_What Information We Collect, Where it is Gathered, and How it is Used_

_Personally Identifiable Information:   _We collect personally identifiable information. In general, our Site allows you to Contact Us, Speak Your Mind, User Submissions and Facebook Social Plugin.  These services may require that you provide us with personally identifiable information such as your name and email address.  Listed below is a list of services where we gather personal information and details on how the information is used.

#### Contact Us Submission

BAM requests personally identifiable information collected from you to contact BAM.  To contact BAM, you must enter your name and email through the Contact Us Form.  You may also provide Your Company name, Subject and Your Message.  This information is used to allow BAM to contact you, improve content of the App, customize the content you see, and any other customer service that you may request from us.  The Contact Us Form also allows you to voluntarily upload submissions that you may want to publish on BAM such as blog posts or other content.  All submissions are subject to the WEBSITE AND USER SUBMISSIONS POLICY OF BAM.

#### Speak Your Mind/User Submissions

BAM encourages you to Speak Your Mind.  User Submissions can take the form of comments, video, quotes and photos.  All User Submissions are voluntary.

Information you reveal on the Site is at your own discretion and it is encouraged that you not communicate to BAM and its Users any information the dissemination of which could be harmful to you.

BAM requests your name, email, website (if applicable) and comments for Speak Your Mind.  Your name and email are required to Speak Your Mind.  Your name will be made public in your Speak Your Mind.

#### Facebook Social Plugin

BAM utilizes a Facebook Social Plugin to further connect with Users.  For more information about Facebook Social Plugins we encourage you to review Facebook’s policies:  <http://www.facebook.com/help/340599879348142/>

When you Like us through the social plugin, your profile picture as well as your name may appear on the Facebook plugin on our Site.  Any other information you share is governed by your Facebook privacy settings.  We encourage you to review your privacy settings before Liking our page on Facebook or through the Facebook Social Plugin on the BAM Site.

#### Children

PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF YOUNG CHILDREN IS ESPECIALLY IMPORTANT TO US. OUR SITE IS GEARED TOWARDS ADULTS.  IN NO EVENT SHOULD THE SITE BE USED BY A CHILD.  BAM DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13 NOR DOES BAM SHARE SUCH INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES. CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 18 MAY USE THE SITE ONLY WITH THE INVOLVEMENT OF A PARENT OR GUARDIAN. IF WE BECOME AWARE THAT WE HAVE COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM A CHILD UNDER AGE 13 WITHOUT VERIFICATION OF PARENTAL CONSENT, BAM WILL TAKE STEPS TO REMOVE THAT INFORMATION.

##### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

The Site uses Analytic tools to track user information.  While we will outline the data gathered by Analytic tools, as with all third party applications, please refer to their [privacy policy here](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html). _          _

Although such information is not personally identifiable, it may be possible to determine from an IP address a visitor’s Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of the visitor’s point of connectivity as well as other statistical usage data.  Your IP address and other non-personally identifiable information also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and Site usage trends. This information helps us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the Site.

We also may share aggregated statistical data and other non-personally identifiable information with our current and potential business partners, advertisers, sponsors and with our service providers.  BAM will not, intentionally, disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that could identify you personally.

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure

BAM won’t share your personal information with other companies, nor will we rent, sell or exchange your email address and information unless otherwise provided:

##### Service Providers

We work with third parties who provide services, including but not limited to website hosting, e-commerce affiliation, data analysis, emailing and other services of an administrative nature. Personally identifiable information is shared with such third parties for the purpose of providing such services.

##### Third Parties

We may use selected reputable third parties for marketing, targeting and analysis purposes.  Some of these third parties may be given access to some, or all, of the information that you provide to us and may use cookies or other tracking technologies in connection with providing their services.  However, these companies do not have an independent right to share this information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated infromation (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Emails from BAM and the Site itself, may contain links to other Internet websites, including sites that may or may not be owned or operated by BAM. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such sites’ use of any information (such as IP number, browser type or operating system) collected when email recipients or Site visitors click through links to those sites. If you visit such websites, we encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of the sites.

##### Legal Obligation to Provide Information

Subject to applicable law, we reserve the right to release information concerning any Site visitor where such visitor is believed to be in violation of his or her obligations to us, is partaking (or is suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, in response to civil subpoenas and discovery requests, to protect the interests of BAM, our customers or others, and as otherwise permitted or required by law.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.  If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.  If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

#### **DELETING YOU PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You may request to have your information deleted by BAM and BAM will do so within a reasonable amount of time.  The non-personal information aggregated by the analytics will remain as, among other reasons, BAM has no control over that information.

##### What Choices Do I Have?

  * If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate by unsubscribing on the emails received, by indicating so on the Contact Us Form, or by contacting us. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the BAM Site, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.
  * You may contact us regarding removal of any of your information.

#### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

BAM may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site and sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Site after such changes have been first noticed.  If you have unsubscribed from all email communications from BAM, we will not email you changes to the Privacy Policy.  You will still, however, be subject to the Privacy Policy changes.

##### Security

BAM takes every precaution to ensure that your information is secure. We utilize the industry standard security protocol. All of your information is encrypted using this secure server for maximum security.

If you have any questions about this Policy, the data collection and usage practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, or if you wish to report a violation of this Policy, please contact:

#### **For privacy concerns please email:**

Email: [privacy@beingamom.life](mailto:privacy@beingamom.life)
